hongkongpost.com 1999-11-09

# Hongkong Post - Privacy Policy Statement

* * *

Hongkong Post pledges to meet fully, and where possible exceed, internationally recognised standards of personal data privacy protection, in complying with the requirements of the [Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance](http://www.pco.org.hk/ord/index.html). In doing so, we will ensure compliance by our staff with the strictest standards of security and confidentiality. 

When you visit our web site, we record your visit only as a 'hit' and do not collect any personal identifiable information about you. The 'hit' information is to allow us to compile general statistics to show the number of visitors to our site. 

We collect personal data from our site visitors on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name, telephone number, address or e-mail address. The information is used only by us for the purposes stated in the respective screens which we invite you to provide your data. We do not use your personal data for any other purposes without your prior consent unless such use is permitted or required by law. 

Our general policy is to disclose no personal identifiable information to third parties except as required by law. 

All personal data you provide to us is secured on our web site with restricted access by authorised personnel only. Our online ordering process uses SET protocol link for data transmission so as to protect your data which may be of security concerns to you. 

From time to time, we may use information we collect about you to e-mail to you promotional materials regarding our products. If you do not wish to receive further promotional e-mails from us, please e-mail to us at [hkpo@hkpo.gcn.gov.hk](mailto:hkpo@hkpo.gcn.gov.hk?subject=Do%20not%20wish%20to%20receive%20further%20promotional%20e-mail) or write to us at Hongkong Post, 2 Connaught Place, Central, Hong Kong. 

* * *
